The next thing I am going to show you is called a step touch.
You can do the step touch to the front to the side and to the back.
We're going to start in the front.
Make sure you're in good posture.
What you want to do is make sure your knees are bent.
Chest is lifted we're going to bring one foot forward and touch.
When you touch just put a little weight into it.
Step, touch put a little weight into it and your hips going to come forward.
So again when you come forward step, touch.
Just put a little weight into it when you touch.
Step, touch.
Step touch this is step touch forward and to forward.
Forward, forward, forward, forward and next we're going step touch the side.
So just step touch and when we put our foot down you just want to put a little pressure in to it so step, touch, step, touch, step, touch, step, touch this is step touch to the side and now we're going to bring it back.
Back with the left leg and we touch we're just going to put a little pressure into the foot and down.
Step back pressure into the foot and back and bring it back touch, touch, touch bring it forward touch, touch, touch, touch out to the side touch, touch, touch, touch and back.
Three, four, five, six, seven and eight step touch.